https://www.cannontrading.com/company/privacy-statement

Open an Account
Contact Us
Why Trade with Cannon?
Service Details
Why Cannon Trading?
E-Futures
FireTip (Mac Compatible)
CQG Trader
CTS T4 (Future Spreads)
OptionVue
CTS Options Pro (Options Spreads)
Options Trading 101
What's Your Trading Blood Type?
Beginner's Guide To Trading Futures
What is Commodity Trading?
Trading Library
Sign Up For Our Market Newsletter
Help & Support
How Cannon Trading Company, Inc. safeguards your privacy online.
Futures Trading >
Company > Privacy Statement
Recommended Platforms:
TransAct AT |
E-Futures |
Trade Navigator
We are committed to safeguarding your privacy online.
We at Cannon Trading recognize the importance of protecting your personal information and financial interests.
As a financial institution and a member of the N.F.A., Cannon Trading must obtain personal information about you. This information assists us in servicing your account. We realize you may have concerns about what we do with this information and the financial information you provide regarding your account.
Your Personal Information
Cannon Trading does not collect personally identifying information about you, except when you knowingly provide it.
Your personal information will only be used to service your account, to improve our service to you, to fill any and all requests by you and to inform you of products and services which may be of interest to you.
We only share information as a part of normal business operations and as a part of normal legal/regulatory purposes required by the Internal Revenue Service, N.F.A.,CFTC and other regulatory and governmental entities.
We do not sell you personal information to third parties.
Links to Other Websites
The Cannon Trading Website contains links to other Websites. Once you link to another site, you are subject to the policies of the new site.
Our Guarantee
Cannon Trading is a legitimate business, all transactions are safe and secure and your privacy is protected.
HAVE A QUESTION?
Featured On
________
Doing Business With
See more...
Loading
10
10
